djhungama.net 2019-08-11

# Privacy Policy | DJ Hungama

##  Privacy Policy

Your use of our Internet sites or any of the products or services offered on those sites (collectively, the “Services”) is subject to these Terms of Use (these “Terms”). We may modify these Terms at any time without notice to you by posting revised Terms on our sites. Your use of our sites constitutes your binding acceptance of these Terms, including any modifications that we make. Some of the Services may be subject to additional posted conditions. Your use of those Services is subject to those conditions, which are incorporated into these Terms by reference. In the event of an inconsistency between these Terms and any additional posted conditions, the provisions of the additional conditions shall control.

We have the right, but not the obligation, to take any of the following actions in our sole discretion at any time and for any reason without giving you any prior notice: DJHungama Takes NO RESPONISIBILTY of the material downloaded from their website , as the material available on this website is owned by the respective production companies. This site is for Entertainment and Promotional Purposes Only. To Report any kind of abuse, just send your mails toDJHungama.in@gmail.com.

Restrict, suspend or terminate your access to all or any part of our Services; Change, suspend or discontinue all or any part of our Services; Refuse, move or remove any material that you submit to our sites for any reason;

Refuse, move, or remove any content that is available on our sites; Deactivate or delete your accounts and all related information and files in your account; Establish general practices and limits concerning use of our sites You agree that we will not be liable to you or any third party for taking any of these actions.

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. 

The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet. To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies. Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, DJHungama has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

###  Collection of Personal Information

When visiting DJHungama.in , the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. Links to third party Websites We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

###  Changes to this Privacy Statement

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion. If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of DJHungama then you may contact us at DJHungama.in@gmail.com.
